A Guide to the Student Government Association Records, 1915-2015: UA 0007
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Student Government Association Records,
1915-2015
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
JMU Student Government Association
UA 0007
12.74 cubic feet; 37 boxes
The Student Government Association Records consist of 12 cubic feet of material relating to the activities of the James Madison University's Student Government Association from its establishment as the Student Association of the State Normal School for Women at Harrisonburg in 1915 until 2015.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection. Collection is open for research with the exception of certain records protected by the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA), particularly those in Series 8: Disciplinary Reports. FERPA protection of student records ends with the death of the student. Therefore, records are opened for research 80 years after their creation when it is presumed that the student is deceased.
Media is inaccessible pending reformating.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the James Madison University Special Collections Library to use this collection (library-special@jmu.edu).
Acquisition Information
The material in this collection was donated by members of James Madison University's Student Government Association in several different accessions between 1993 and 2015. The earlier accessions (1993-2001) were previously processed and assigned archival collection numbers SGA 93-0401, SGA 93-1019, and SGA 2001-1010. These materials were reprocessed along with the later accessions and combined into one larger collection, UA 0007. Additional accessions (2015-0830, 2015-0828, and 2015-0505) were added to the collection in November 2018. On May 1st, 2019, an additional 2 storage boxes were donated by SGA Communications Director, Halle Forbes.
Accruals
This collection may receive additions.
Administrative History
James Madison University's Student Government Association was established in February 1915 as the school's first student government. Although rumblings of self-government began with the founding of the school in 1908, it took a fair amount of effort to bring this idea to fruition. The roots of the university's SGA derive from the student Honor Council which began in the 1909-1910 school year. Students involved in the Honor Council began to create an unofficial student government that although unable to act in an official capacity, was instrumental in helping to bring about student support for self-government. By 1914, a small group of students worked together to draft a constitution for the planned student government organization and presented this constitution to the faculty. After completing revisions suggested by the faculty, the constitution was presented and voted on by the entire student body February 25, 1915 and as a result, the Student Association of the State Normal School at Harrisonburg was established. This first iteration of the organization required that the entire student body act as a member. Additionally, the Honor Committee was converted into the first Executive Board. This Executive Board included three officers (president, vice-president, and secretary), and several elected members of each class.
As the school and student population grew so did the organization and it eventually became unrealistic for the entire student body to act as members of the organization. Complications also arose within the organization with the introduction of full-time male students in 1946. At the time, it did not seem appropriate for men and women to govern students of the opposite sex. As a result, the male students decided to create their own self-government in 1950, labeling their organization the Men's Student Government Organization. The female students likewise formally relabeled their existing organization the Women's Student Government Association in 1953 to better distinguish the separation between the two groups; however, they rarely included this additional identifier. While the two groups worked together on many matters through the 50s and 60s, the organizations formally combine in 1970, creating the current manifestation of the Student Government Association.
As of 2015, the SGA at JMU is made up of appointed members on the Executive Staff, Representatives, and At-Large Senators. Elected members include Class Council Senators, College Senators, and Area Residence Senators. The mission: The Student Government Association of James Madison University is an organization dedicated to collaborating with all members of its community to advocate for student opinion, while fostering a proactive, inclusive environment.
Scope and Content
This collection documents the activities of James Madison University's Student Government Association in Harrisonburg, Virginia from 1915-2015. The collection developed from seven different accessions from the Student Government Association received in the 1990s and early 2000s and contains a wide range of material which is organized according to physical type or corresponding to subject. Much of the material in this collection derives from different meetings within the organization including: the Student Council, Student Senate, Execution Board, Senate and Council Committees, and others. A large amount of the collection is administrative material regarding the work of these different internal groups as well as the procedures which govern them. Similarly, these different internal meetings produced a fair amount of the minutes, committee reports, and legislative files found in the collection. In addition to these materials, there are also a large amount of financial files related to the budget of SGA and other on campus organizations. This collection also consists of correspondence to and from different members of the SGA usually regarding issues of student conduct on and off campus. The last major section of the collection contains photographs, scrapbooks, and ephemera memorializing different SGA events. Further descriptions of the material can be found in the series descriptions. The collection has been arranged into twelve series.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into 11 series:
Series 1: Administrative, 1915-2015
Series 2: Committees, 1931-2015
Series 3: Correspondence, 1955-2003
Series 4: Policies and Regulations, 1931-1971
Series 5: Minutes, 1929-2012
Series 6: Legislative Files, 1989-2012
Series 7: Financial Files, 1987-2014
Series 8: Disciplinary Reports, 1922-1973
Series 9: Photographs, 2000-2014
Series 10: Scrapbooks, 2001-2009
Series 11: Ephemera, 1930-2015
All series are arranged chronologically
Related Materials
Some of the material in this collection can be viewed on Special Collections' Student Government Association Digital Exhibit published on-line in April 2015. https://omeka.lib.jmu.edu/specialcollections/collections/show/2
Bibliography
Raymond Dingledine, Madison College: The First Fifty Years, 1908-1958 (Harrisonburg, Virginia: Madison College, 1959).
Index Terms
Subjects:
State Normal School for Women at Harrisonburg (Harrisonburg, Va.) -- Students; State Normal School for Women at Harrisonburg (Harrisonburg, Va.) -- History; State Teachers College at Harrisonburg (Harrisonburg, Va.) -- Students; State Teachers College at Harrisonburg (Harrisonburg, Va.) -- History; Madison College -- Students; Madison College -- History; James Madison University -- Students; James Madison University -- History; College student government; College student government -- Elections; Student activities; Student activities -- Finance; Student activities -- Handbooks, manuals, etc; Student activities -- Virginia -- Harrisonburg; College students; School discipline; Student participation in administration
- Series 1: Administrative, 1915-2015
  Scope and Content
  This is the largest series in the collection and contains material related to the function and organization of SGA, featuring a variety of documents from 1923-2013, with the bulk of this series is from 1990-2013. There is a large gap in the material around 1980s. The first folder in the series, containing the organization's first constitution and by-laws, is not original to the collection. The document was located in the 1915 Faculty Minutes in the Board of Visitors Collection, 1908-2004 (PR 99-1122), photocopied, and added to the collection on March 25, 2015. This series additionally contains some interesting material related to student strikes which took place on campus in 1969 and 1970. There is particular information related to Jay Rainey, one of the student leaders, as well as SGA's Committee on Student Protest. Other materials to note in this series are documents from the early 2000s which relate to the sexual assault research on college campuses, reports related to the impact of Title IX on campus, and SGA research regarding the Forrest Hill Riot in 2000, which resulted in a conflict between the Harrisonburg Police Department and students at a spring block party.
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the Student Association of the State Normal School at Harrisonburg (Photocopy), 1915 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the Student Association (Agness Browne Stribling's copy), 1915 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Southern Intercollegiate Association, 1923-1936 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Constitutions of Old Organizations, 1930-1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - SGA Organizational Chart, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Student Evaluation of Madison College, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Orientation and Retreat, 1956-1957, 1959-1965, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Assemblies, 1959-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Constitutions Revised, 1959-1962, 1974, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Events Leading to the Strike of 1970, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Demonstration, May 1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Demonstration recordings, May 6, 1972
    - Original audiocassette: North Side Wilson and Sen. Byrd's Speech, recorded by Dr. Grant O. Rush, May 6, 1972 (Box 1, Audiocassette UA0007-CS-001)
    - Original audiocassette: South Side Wilson and Sen. Byrd's Speech, recorded by Elger Wilkerson, May 6, 1972 (Box 1, Audiocassette UA0007-CS-002)
  - Constitutions and House Rules, 1990-1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bond Issue, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sexual Assault Research, 1991,1993-1995, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Sexual Assault Research, 1991,1993-1995, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board of Visitors and University Council Reports, 1992,1994,1996-2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board of Visitors and University Council Reports, 1992,1994,1996-2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Archive, 1992,1996, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Senate Retreat Fall, 1995, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Senator/Social Club, 1995-1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - SGA President Transition Handbook, 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Breeze Records, 1997-1998, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - New Archive, 1997, 1999, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Loose Material, 1997-1999, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Application Forms, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Fall Varsity Retreat, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - From Retreat, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Information, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - University Center, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Retreat, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - SGA Leadership Scholarship, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Winter Retreat, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Camp Horizons/ Senate Retreat, 1999, 2001, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Breeze Information Sheets, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Camp Horizons Retreat, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Casework, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Clubs and Organizations, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Elections, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Events and Conferences, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Forrest Hill, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Freshman Survey, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Major Elections, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Mark's Stuff, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Minor Elections, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Pamphlet, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Platforms, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Senate Retreat, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - SGA Website, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Senator Folders/ White Copies, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Appendices for Forrest Hill Report, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Forrest Hill Riot Research, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Forrest Hill Student Responses, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Scrap for Handbook, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Sports Team Cuts Research, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Student Leadership Alliance Documents, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Election Documents, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - To File, 2000, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 9-11 Relief Effort, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 30 Year Committee, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Board of Visitor Reports, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - City Council Agendas, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Class Council Officers, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Commons for the Commons, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Discuss Executive, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Rose's House Reception, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - End-of-Year Banquet, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - SGA At-a-Glance, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Massanutten Executive Retreat, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - SEALS, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - SEALS/Class Councilors Retreat, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - SEALS Program, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - SGA 9-11-01 Response, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - SGA Handbook, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - SGA Reports, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Appointed Positions, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Background Research, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Breeze Articles, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Calendar, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - New Archives, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - SGA Handbook, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Senate Documents, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Senior Class Challenge, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - SGA Press Releases, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Beginning of Year, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - SGA Certificates, 2001, 2003, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - SGA Press Releases, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Travel Authorizations, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - The Student Government Association Senate Handbook, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Student Leadership Alliance, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - President Stoney's Legislative Issues, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Email/Contact Information, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Handbook, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - SGA Handbook, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - The Breeze SGA Articles, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - International Students, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Legal Assistance, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Lights/Blue Lights, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Lobby Trip-Legislation, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - President Culligan's Project, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Transition Stuff, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - VA21 and SGA Legislative Issues, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - SGA Handbook, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - SGA Treasurer Materials, 2006-2009 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Student Government Association of James Madison University Handbook, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Ring Premiere Committee Applications, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - JMU Student Government Associations Handbook, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Candidate Packets, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Conference on Student Government Associations Applications, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Spring 2009 Treasurer Election, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Spring 2009 Executive and Student Representative to the Board of Visitors Elections, 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Unknown Executive Officer's Notes, 2009-2010 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Virginia21 Legislative Training Day Materials, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - SGA President Transition Handbook (Folder 1 of 2), 2010-2011 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - SGA President Transition Handbook (Folder 2 of 2), 2010-2011 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Minor Elections Information Binder, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Minor Elections Binder, 2011 (Box 1, Cd-r UA0007-OP-001)
  - Student Government Association Constitution, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - SGA Constitution, Incomplete, 2013 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - SGA Constitution, Pre-formatted and Signed, 2013 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - SGA Constitution and Student Senate House Rules, 2014-2015 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Archive/Old To Dos, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Constitutional Review, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Giving Campaign Captain Handbook, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Holiday Greetings, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Memorandum Forms, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - NT Server, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - SGA Advisor Survey Responses (Folder 1 of 2), undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - SGA Advisor Survey Responses (Folder 2 of 2), undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Series 2: Committees, 1931-2015
  This series contains material related to the work of the different SGA committees from 1931-2002. There is another large gap of material in the 1980s. The bulk of this series is from the 1960s and 1999-2002. This series also includes information related to the standards of conduct for female students in the 1930s and 1960s, such as proper dating procedures.
  - Standards Committee, 1931-1933, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Committees SGA, 1932, 1953-1960, 1962-1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Student Organization Committee, 1935-1959 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Campus Fee Committee, 1953-1964 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee Reports, 1957-1961 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee Reports, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Advisory Committee for student center, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Student Faculty Relations Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Multicultural Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Student Safety Task Force, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Community Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Action Committee (folder 1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Action Committee (folder 2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - SGA Executive Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Planning and Advisory Committee, 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Planning and Advisory Committee, 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Commissions and Committees, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Director's Response to Centennial Sports Committee Report, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Bus Advisory Committee, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Committee Phone Lists, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Logo Committee, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Madison Athletic Committee, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Speaker, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - SGA Committee Chairman Binder, 2000-2001, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Commissions and Committees, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Commissions and Committees, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Parking Committee/Forum, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Committee Applications/Information, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Advisory Committee, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - SGA Education and Student Life Committee Meeting Materials, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Action Committee (folder 1 of 2), 2014-2015 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Action Committee (folder 2 of 2), 2014-2015 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Series 3: Correspondence, 1955-2003
  This series features correspondence from members of SGA to faculty and students on campus as well as several folders of correspondence to individuals off campus. The material in this series ranges from 1955-1971 with a small concentration from 2003. This series contains a fair amount of historical material, such as: a thank you card from Jackie Kennedy, 1963; material related to fears of communism on college campuses, 1965-1966; a letter from an upset parent regarding Jane Fonda's visit to campus in 1971; correspondence related to the proper conduct of female students during the 1950s and 1960s, especially in terms of interactions with males. This series also contains a collection of correspondence regarding the 2003 Board of Visitors decision to stop supplying students with emergency conception through the health center.
  - Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Off-Campus Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Board of Visitors Debate, 2003, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Series 4: Policies and Regulations, 1931-2000
  This series contains material related to the different standards and regulations applying to the students of the school 1931-1971. Most of the material from this series is from the 1950s and 1960s. These documents provide interesting examples of the different social expectations of men and women during the period as well as the restrictive nature of the school's administration in comparison to current campus regulations. The material from the 2000s relates to the policies student representatives are to follow during meetings of the Student Senate.
  - Rules and Regulations, 1931-1937 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1951, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1962, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1964-1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1967-1971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Student Government Association House Rules, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Parliamentary Procedures, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Series 5: Meeting Minutes, 1929-2012
  This series contains the minutes of the different branches of SGA, particularly Student Senate and the Executive Board, 1922-2012. There are two gaps in this series most notably between 1930-1940 with two smaller gaps in the 1970s and 2000s. These minutes generally provide information such as: meeting agendas, events taking place on campus, SGA members and committee chairs, as well as general insight into the everyday issues discussed in SGA meetings.
  - SGA Minutes, 1929, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - SGA Minutes, 1940-1941, 1946-1949 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Summer Quarter, 1948-1952 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - SGA Minutes, 1950-1952 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Minutes, 1958, 1962-1965 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Minutes, 1958-1966 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Minutes, 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1966-1971 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 1)